Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer.
And his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for
One piece
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down Your
heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm
That legendary place That the end
of the map reveals Is only legendary
Until someone proves it real
Through it all Through all the trouble
and times Through the heartache
and through the pain Know that
I will be there to stand by you
Just like I know you'll stand by me
so come aboard and bring along all your
hopes and dreams together we will find
everything that we're looking for there's
always room for you if
you want to be my friend
Hey, man.
You all right? Try to breathe.
You need a little fresh air.
You want a pillow?
Or maybe some water? Speak.
This is bad. You know what?
I make a great banana pudding.
Want some?
You idiot.
We don't want him to choke to death
on any of your culinary disasters.
Better that than the trots he'd get from
choking down one of your raunchy meat pies.
The reason I won't feed him one of my
meat pies is because after one bite,
he'd think he died and gone to heaven.
Ah!
Don't die yet!
Well, this isn't good. We're in trouble.
No, that was just luck.
Don Krieg is going to get up
and kick his ass any minute now.
Just watch.
Hope he's dead.
So, boy, it's not your funeral yet, is it?
Too bad.
Because one of us has got to go.
Oh, and since I'm here, I'd
really like to pay my respects!
Go to hell!
You bitch!
This can't be happening!
He's taking another fall!
But how?
I've never seen anyone
hit him because they're
usually dead before they get close enough!
The fact is, he might not
actually be invincible
What the hell are you?
Look at that, the kid's pretty good.
Yeah, no kidding.
He's amazing.
Finish him off, Chaw Boy.
Yeah, end it once and for all.
That punk is fighting with Don Krieg
as if he were the same strength.
This can't be real, it's like
I'm watching my own nightmare.
He's supposed to be truly invincible.
Well, if he gets beaten by this little
kid, his reputation will be completely...
Shut up, maggots!
Never doubt me!
What was that?
Finally, he's gonna stop messing
around and step up his game!
The mighty Battlespear!
What was that?
An exploding spear?
Now what?
You gonna try to hide from me?
All right, then, boy.
This should be fun.
My mighty battle spear.
It's different from the one
I was fighting with earlier.
When this thing hits you, you
won't just be wounded and flailing.
You will be blown straight into hell!
That's not a normal spear!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Not in the water!
That spear really sucks!
It explodes every time he hits anything!
what's going on my knees
he's lost way too much blood he
can't fight for much longer this
better end quickly you look tired
too bad guess you should have saved a
little more energy damn if everything
rocking i can't hit him with full
force i've never in my life seen a
more stunning weapon than the mighty
battle spear.
Don Krieg is the only one strong
enough to handle the spear,
since the harder he strikes with it,
the bigger the explosion it causes.
Anyone else would just be completely
destroyed by their own pathetic attack.
It's strength.
His strength is the key.
He causes the kind of
damage no one else can,
because there's just no
one else who can swing
a spear that easily
weighs more than a ton.
That's exactly why Don Krieg is the
most dangerous man in the East Blue.
Now die!
Char-Boy, look out!
Phew, that was really close.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE A LITTLE BUCK!
Choreboy!
That's rough.
I'm not finished with you.
If you hadn't made me so angry, I
would have killed you more quickly.
Damn it.
There's no way that Choreboy
can take much more of this.
That spear is way too powerful.
Now you're wrong.
Even with a hundred thousand more weapons,
our chore boy can still
bring him to his knees?
because he does not know fear.
Ha!
That was too easy.
Now that's impressive.
Stand or fall, life or death.
In a struggle for your very existence,
you cannot have even the slightest
bit of fear or you will be lost.
What are you talking about?
That kid out there...
When he's fighting...
He's not afraid of anything.
Not even death.
Is it just instinct or all a plan?
We'll know soon!
If he lives?
What plan?
Killing himself.
You son of a bitch!
Way to go, Chowboy!
Do it again! Kick his ass!
I told you, today is your funeral!
There is no doubt that Krieg
and his pirates are strong.
But Chorboy has something
they'll never have.
Krieg may have more pirates at his
command than anyone else before him.
He may have terrible weapons that cause
mass destruction to everything in his path.
But he will never have that kid's heart.
What?!
My Battlespear!
What the hell did you do?!
I just punched it in the head five times.
It looks tired.
Maybe it needs a rest.
Now it's my turn.
Now that your little toy's
broken you're nothing to me.
Oh yeah yeah without the
blade it's just a bomb
on a stick and let's face
it that's pretty lame.
You think so?
Sure do.
Fine so what if it is?
Just a bomb on a stick
you're in sad shape kiddo.
I think it'll be more than
enough to blow you to.
You know it?
Sounds to me like this is some sort
of pathetic attempt at a block.
Okay but you're wrong.
Your boy is pretty good, huh?
He might be able to pull it off
This is terrible.
He just shattered the mighty battle spear
It's a miracle he's still alive
after that many explosions.
There's no way he can hold up
Just give up.
Your defeat is imminent.
You see, when you defy me, you
sign your own death warrant!
Hey, up here!
Bastard!
You monkey!
Bounce out of that!
Nice try!
How many weapons does that guy have?
Now come Tom!
I'm wearing wood-steel body armor.
This stuff is practically indestructible.
We'll see about that Tom-Tom pistol!
DONE!
How dare you!
It's useless.
You'll never defeat me!
This armor could take a
million more of your monkey
punches and it wouldn't
have so much as a dent!
Well, we'll just see about that.
He's gone!
I'm right here.
You don't stand a chance, boy.
Real power comes from deadly weapons.
They're the source of true strength.
See, only the strong are meant to live.
And that's me.
Yeah, that's what you think!
It's useless!
Foolish pride will only get you so far!
Bazooka!
That's it?
After all that big talk,
that's all you've got?
No!
I don't believe it!
My armor's cracking!
It doesn't matter.
You're done for, Shura Boy!
It's a trap!
Get out!
Shoot! Shortball!
He's not afraid of anything.
Not even death.
Is it just instinct, or all a plan?
We'll know soon if he lives.
What the?
Oh!
Way to go, Chowboy!
I totally win!
This isn't over yet, boy!
Whoa, he's alive!
You can't escape!
It's a steel net!
It's over!
That's the ocean down there below us!
It looks like I'll be getting the
last laugh after all, char boy!
Take him down, dog!
Make that little brat pay!
Hey, get him!
Now I got that jerk
right where I want him!
He hasn't even flinched.
How can he stay so cold?
Time for me to end this!
Right now!
Now, Kuma Kuma!
Giant hammer!
No!
Tang Creek was defeated!
How could this have happened?
You're awesome, Choreboy! Yay!
He kicked his ass!
He won!
He really won! Oh, wow!
I gotta be dreaming!
That's Tang Creek we're talking about!
I know!
Who'd have thought that kid had it in him?
What is it? What's going on? Hey!
Rise and shine!
Craig was beaten!
Bet you never thought you'd see the day!
What?
Are you done daydreaming
yet? Come on! Save that, kid!
He can't swim!
What?
Those with the power of the
Devil Fruit are hated by the sea,
so they lose their ability to swim.
What are you saying?
He'll just sink?
You could have told me that
sooner, you worthless old geezer!
What if it's already too late?!
you said you wouldn't die
you truly believe that
right well you'll have
to do better than that
If you want to beat me...
Because I don't think it's
time for me to die just yet!
These guys...
Zoro!
Now this fight would end
was clear from the start.
Why choose death?
Don't be stupid!
Give up your ambition and live!
I don't know, but I will not run.
Even if I retreat a single step, I would
be shattering the promises I've made.
I can't run.
I would lose my honor.
You see, without that, there
would be nothing left for me here.
Even with a hundred thousand more weapons,
our chore boy can still
bring him to his knees?
because he does not know fear.
Krieg may have more
pirates at his command.
He may have terrible weapons that cause
mass destruction to everything in his path.
Hey, Choreboy, don't you die on me!
Don, are you okay?
Please, tell us it's an act!
Don Krieg has been defeated.
This can't be happening.
He's the mighty ruler of the East Blue.
Yeah, well now he's down for the count.
Have a look at him and see for yourself.
That fancy armor of his got all busted up,
and he was out as soon as he hit the deck.
What, do you think we're lying to you?
Go ahead and look.
He was the only man I ever really admired.
How foolish. Now he's lost.
Hey, hold on.
If you move now, the poison will set in.
Hey, buddy, don't die.
Chore boy.
Chore boy, can you hear me?
Don't die.
You still have a lot of
things to do with your life.
Please don't die!
Are you kidding?
You really are something else. No!
I'm the strongest!
I win!
I'm the greatest!
I'm the best!
No one defeats me!
No!
Just stay down! Stop him!
He's not even conscious!
Please, don't! Stop!
I have to win!
I have to!
Kill! Enemy!
I'll fight until victory is mine!
Don Krieg, we lost.
Commander!
Let's leave now, while we
still have a shred of dignity.
Thanks for everything, Sanji.
Sure, now leave and don't ever come back.
Hey, Sanji, you don't owe me any favors.
But when the kid wakes up,
tell him I said I'll see
him on the Grand Line.
But you...
That's where I want to go
with the time I have left.
It's the only thing I care about.
The only thing that keeps me going.
It would seem that Donkring's obsession
with the Grand Line has become mine as well.
It's silly.
I know that, but it's my dream.
With this poison in my veins, I
may only have a few hours to live.
But I feel free somehow, like now I can
live those last few moments on my own terms.
To hell with loyalty to Don Krieg.
My devotion to him was just an
escape from forging my own destiny.
Once your heart is set,
and you pursue all your dreams with
every last fiber of what you are,
you will never again feel
lost or hopeless or afraid.
I learned all that from a brave tour boy.
Hey, you guys!
Give him the boat we use
to go grocery shopping!
Come on!
Are you stupid or something?
Why do we have to give a perfectly
good boat to a bunch of pirates?
And what's going to happen
to all our grocery shopping?
Jackass! Hattie's right!
Let them swim wherever they're going to!
Go get that grocery boat now!
Alright, fine!
Stop shouting!
Okay, okay, we'll go get it!
It's gonna sink!
Why did I hesitate?
What was I so worried about?
When I think about it, I
can't help but feel stupid.
Well then, we gratefully accept this boat,
and my right to assume
there's no need to return it.
It's yours.
Don't ever come back
here, not for anything.
Not even to return this boat.
He's right!
And don't you ever forget, this is
the restaurant where the cooks fight!
The Baratier!
The cooks there sure mean business.
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure!
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me!
I had to find my way to that place.
Before someone could beat me!
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go!
La la la la.
My only dream.
La la la la la.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true!
But if the world ever changes,
I call out your name!
We could return to the time
when everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade!
Waiting for that one true dream?